<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>java on whathebea</title>
    <link>https://whathebea.github.io/tags/java/</link>
    <description>Recent content in java on whathebea</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Beatriz Gracia</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whathebea.github.io/tags/java/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to use Junit and Mockito for unit testing in Java</title>
      <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-26-22-using-junit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-26-22-using-junit/</guid>
      <description>I know today is Sunday but I really felt like writing something. It seems like I can&amp;rsquo;t stop thinking about coding and trying to perfect everything that I am learning. This may be personal but, does anyone else feel this way? Before my internship although I was very dedicated it seems that now I am much more focused. Also, I lost two Valorant matches in a row so I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a bit down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting an API (Java Spring) to an Android application</title>
      <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-21-22-studying-internship-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-21-22-studying-internship-api/</guid>
      <description>It has been a while since my last post but I swear I haven&amp;rsquo;t given up! It&amp;rsquo;s quite the opposite, actually. I had to do a project for my internship program which was basically creating a Rest API and connecting it to an Android Application. As it turns out, connecting an API to an app is more of a chore than I thought it would be. I hope I can stick with web development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I have been studying</title>
      <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/what-studying/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/what-studying/</guid>
      <description>I believe that, nowadays, writing a blog is just one way to make myself aware that I am studying a lot. Maybe I will talk a lot about myself, but the I.T field can sometimes be very harsh on you (or me). I am aware that, being an intern, I don&amp;rsquo;t have the same hardships as regular employees, but it can still be hard. I also feel like there are a lot of commas, but to be honest, I never properly learned how to use commas in English and, that being said, Grammarly is correcting it all for me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
