<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on whathebea</title>
    <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on whathebea</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Beatriz Gracia</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whathebea.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A little bit about CI/CD and Jenkins</title>
      <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-31-22-ci-cd-jenkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-31-22-ci-cd-jenkins/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel like making a huge introduction to this post. I will just talk a little bit about what I studied today. If you have already read Jenkins documentation you can probably skip this, I just wanted to explain it to myself.
What is CI/CD? CI CI stands for Continuous Integration and for that you basically merge your code into a main branch as often as possible. This way it&amp;rsquo;s easier to detect bugs and you can fix them before they get to production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servlets and JSP</title>
      <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-28-22-servlets-and-jsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-28-22-servlets-and-jsp/</guid>
      <description>Today I decided to study about Servlets and JSP a little bit and I will talk a little bit about them.
Servlets What are servlets? A servlet is a Java class that extends the HttpServlet class. It is used to handle HTTP requests and responses.
When are servlets used? Theyb are used to create dynamic web pages and applications. Dynamic web pages are web pages that are generated by the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Junit and Mockito for unit testing in Java</title>
      <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-26-22-using-junit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-26-22-using-junit/</guid>
      <description>I know today is Sunday but I really felt like writing something. It seems like I can&amp;rsquo;t stop thinking about coding and trying to perfect everything that I am learning. This may be personal but, does anyone else feel this way? Before my internship although I was very dedicated it seems that now I am much more focused. Also, I lost two Valorant matches in a row so I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a bit down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting an API (Java Spring) to an Android application</title>
      <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-21-22-studying-internship-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-21-22-studying-internship-api/</guid>
      <description>It has been a while since my last post but I swear I haven&amp;rsquo;t given up! It&amp;rsquo;s quite the opposite, actually. I had to do a project for my internship program which was basically creating a Rest API and connecting it to an Android Application. As it turns out, connecting an API to an app is more of a chore than I thought it would be. I hope I can stick with web development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The basics of angular</title>
      <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-13-22-angular/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/10-13-22-angular/</guid>
      <description>A new day! Today is Thursday, October 13th. I started the day by studying Angular for a couple hours. So, today I am going to talk a bit about Angular.
Today I learned about: Components Components are apparently a big part of Angular development! You can create them in the cl or create them by hand. Obviously, creating them with the cl command is a lot easier. The command is the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I have been studying</title>
      <link>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/what-studying/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whathebea.github.io/posts/what-studying/</guid>
      <description>I believe that, nowadays, writing a blog is just one way to make myself aware that I am studying a lot. Maybe I will talk a lot about myself, but the I.T field can sometimes be very harsh on you (or me). I am aware that, being an intern, I don&amp;rsquo;t have the same hardships as regular employees, but it can still be hard. I also feel like there are a lot of commas, but to be honest, I never properly learned how to use commas in English and, that being said, Grammarly is correcting it all for me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
